Badland is a western film directed by Justin Lee.
Detective Matthias Breecher, hired to track down the worst of the
Confederate war criminals, roams the Old West seeking justice.
His resolve is tested when he meets a determined pioneer
woman who is far more than she seems.
Reginald Cooke, played by Bruce Dern.
Sarah Cooke, played by Mira Sorvino.
Matthias Breecher, played by Kevin Makely.
Huxley Wainwright, played by Jeff Fahey.
Harlan Red, played by Wes Studi.
Senator Benjamin Burke, played by Tony Todd.
Badland is a 2019 American Western film set more than a
decade after the American Civil War.
Written and directed by Justin Lee, it depicts a Pinkerton detective who has been sent west to find
several former Confederate soldiers who committed atrocious acts during the Civil War.